shesconnectedconference.com 2014-02-15

# ShesConnected Conference 2012 | Privacy Policy

### What This Privacy Policy Covers

We at ShesConnected Multimedia, Corp. (“ShesConnected”,” the “Company,” “we,” “us,” “our”) understand that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. For that reason, we follow a privacy policy that applies to your use of all of the products, services, and Web sites offered by ShesConnected or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies. In line with that policy, we want to let you know how we treat personal information that we collect and receive from users of websites owned and operated by Mobile Momma (or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies), including, without limitation, [www.ShesConnected.com](http://www.shesconnected.com/), and [www.ShesConnectednetwork.com](http://www.shesconnectednetwork.com/) (collectively, the “Company Web Sites”). Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number.

This Privacy Policy covers the following:

  * The information we collect and use, including how we generally use that information.
  * What we share and disclose and why and to whom.
  * Our promotions, sweepstakes and contests
  * What “Cookies and Web Beacons” are and how we use them.
  * How to update and delete your account information.
  * How you will be notified of changes to our Privacy Policy.
  * How and whom to contact if you have questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy applies only to the Company Websites. When linking from the Company Web sites to other Web sites, if you have privacy concerns, we urge you to review the privacy policies of those sites.

**It’s also important to note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to information that you post, yourself, in public areas of the Company Websites.** For example, if you choose to let other people see your list of goals, your name, and your answers to the profile questions, or if you post information or comments on a discussion board, that information will be made public. Your messages and other information you make available in public areas of the Company Websites will be seen by people and organizations not related to or controlled by us, and may be used by others to contact you.

* * *

### Information Collection and Use

We collect personal information from you whenever you interact with us, such as when you:

  * register with one or more of the Company Websites,
  * use our products or services,
  * enter promotions or sweepstakes,

We may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

  * When you register, we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register with one or more of the Company Websites and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. You are free to use the Company Websites without registering or setting up a personal account (e.g. a ShesConnected account); however, some of our services and web pages are available only to those who are registered users.
  * We collect information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners.
  * We automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the pages you request.
  * We may also collect information about you from other sources, such as newspapers, blogs, instant messaging services, and other users of the Company Websites through the operation of the service (e.g., photo captions) in order to provide you with more useful information and a more personalized experience.
  * We use your personal information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. In short, the information you provide us can help us to understand how to make the Company Web Sites more convenient and useful to you.
  * By using any of the Company Websites, you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States.
  * In general, we provide access to your personal information only to our employees and contractors who we believe need that access in order to do their jobs and to provide products or services to you.

* * *

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

User profile information including screen name and location displayed to people in order to facilitate user interaction in our online social networking communities.We do not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you request, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with us under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help us communicate with you about offers from us and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.
  * We may sometimes share aggregate non-personal information with third parties such as the media, advertisers, and government agencies. This aggregate information is typically in the form of statistics, such as numbers of our users who live in a particular state or fall within a particular age group. Such aggregate information is gathered from individual users’ information but is not traceable to any specific identifiable user.
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, or as otherwise required or permitted by law.
  * If the Company is required to transfer personally identifiable information to a third party in the event of a sale, merger, assignment, joint venture or other transfer or disposition of a portion or all of the assets or stock of ShesConnected or its affiliated entities (including, without limitation, in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings).
  * In order to allow access to our systems to third parties providing necessary technical services when such access is required in order to provide those services.

Please note, however, that we reserve the right to share any personally identifiable or other information about you which you provide to (or which is gathered by) the Company or the Company Websites with any or all of its subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively, our “Affiliates”) (subject to certain opt-out rights provided in your account profile with respect to disclosures of personally identifiable information to Affiliates for their direct marketing uses). We will also have access to any such information which you provide to (or which is gathered by) the web sites of any of our Affiliates.

* * *

### Our Advertisers

We do not share your personal information with our advertisers. However, the advertising we display is targeted to users of particular services and content. So if you view or click on a targeted ad, the advertiser (or other companies affiliated with the advertiser) may assume that you meet the targeting criteria – for example, women from a particular geographic area or with children or grandchildren of a certain age.

* * *

### Promotions, Sweepstakes and Contests

From time to time, we or a partner may sponsor a promotion, sweepstake or contest on one or more of the Company Websites. Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address, or to answer questions in order to participate. We may transfer personal information to certain ad partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply.

* * *

### Cookies and Web Beacons

The Company Websites, like many Web sites, uses cookies to prepare customized Web pages for you. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser. By default, we use a persistent cookie that stores your login ID (but not your password) to make it easier for you to login when you come back to the Company Websites. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature. With cookies in place, whenever you use your Web browser (such as Internet Explorer, AOL, or Mozilla Firefox) to connect to the Company Websites, our systems are able to recognize you. This enables us to present you with custom Web pages. So, for example, instead of seeing just a generic welcome page, you see a welcome page with your name on it and information that relates to where you live (your zip code) and content, products or services that reflect your interests.

In addition to our cookies, when you visit the Company Websites, your computer may receive cookies from our advertisers, and from other sites displayed as search results or links. The cookies inserted by those third parties are not covered by this Privacy Policy, but rather, by the policies of those advertisers and outside Web sites.

You can set up your browser to reject cookies or tell you when a cookie has been sent. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of the Company Websites’ interactive features, and we hope you will leave them turned on.

The Company Websites also uses web beacons (also known as action tags or single pixel gifs) to access our cookies inside and outside our Web pages and in connection with our products and services. A web beacon is a transparent image placed on a web page that sends a signal when a person visits that page. This enables us to assess the popularity and effectiveness of the material posted on the Company Websites. We may also use web beacons in connection with e-mails sent to our users, to let us know whether and when the e-mail was opened. No personal information is transmitted through web beacons.

* * *

### Disclaimer

You post User Content (as defined in the ShesConnected Terms of Use) on the Company Websites at your own risk. Although we allow you to set privacy options that limit access to your pages, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other Users with whom you may choose to share your pages and information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that User Content you post on the Site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Company Websites. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of User Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other Users have copied or stored your User Content.

* * *

### Your Ability to Update and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences Including Opt Out Rights

  * You can update your Account Information, including your biographical and profile information, at any time, by going to your user setting page. While there, you can make choices about how your information may be used by the Company and its affiliates to provide marketing offers to you. You may opt out of such marketing communications. These preferences do not apply to communications that are directly related to your registration with ShesConnected, or the fulfillment of a specific transaction you have requested (for example, a service advisory from the Company, or an acknowledgment of a purchase order). If you choose to opt out of certain disclosure options, you may be unable to use certain features on the Company Websites.
  * You may request deletion of your account by sending a message to [Support@shesconnected.com](mailto:Support@shesconnected.com). Please note that some information may remain in our records after deletion of your account.
  * New categories of marketing communications may be added to the My Account page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications on these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive.
  * During the time period in which you maintain an account on one or more of the Company Websites, we reserve the right to send you certain important communications relating to our services, such as service announcements and administrative messages, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving these important communications.
  * You can terminate your account at any time by sending a request to [Help@ShesConnected.com](mailto:Help@ShesConnected.com).
  * If you choose to use our invitation service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. We store this information to send this one-time email, to register a friend connection if your invitation is accepted, and to track the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at [info@shesconnected.com](mailto:info@shesconnected.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.
  * We take appropriate precautions to protect our users’ information. Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number or your password), we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). (To learn more about SSL, go to <http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Secure_Sockets_Layer>). Because email and instant messaging are not recognized as secure communications, we request that you not send private information to us by email or instant messaging services. If you have any questions about the security of the Company Websites, please contact us at [info@shesconnected.com](mailto:info@shesconnected.com).

* * *

### Links to Other Sites

  * Users will find advertising or other content on the Company Websites that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the contents of, or links that appear on, these sites. In addition, these sites or services, including their contents and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies, or no policy (policies) at all. Once you link to another site from a Company Website, you are subject to the terms and conditions of that site, including, but not limited to, its Internet privacy policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any third party sites or services before providing any of them with your personal information.

* * *

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

  * This Privacy Policy may be changed from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account or by placing a prominent notice on the applicable Company Website.

* * *

### Questions and Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at:  
ShesConnected  
971 Concord Avenue  
[email] [feedback@shesconnected.com](mailto:feedback@shesconnected.com)
